https://psemc.com/privacy/

Quicklinks:
PACIFIC SCIENTIFIC ENERGETIC MATERIALS COMPANY
Privacy Notice – Download our privacy notice here.
Terms of Use
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS (“TERMS”) CAREFULLY BEFORE YOU USE THIS WEBSITE. USING THIS WEBSITE INDICATES THAT YOU ACCEPT THESE TERMS; IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS, DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE. IF YOU BREACH ANY OF THE TERMS, YOUR AUTHORIZATION TO USE THIS WEBSITE WILL IMMEDIATELY TERMINATE AND YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY DESTROY ALL DOWNLOADED OR PRINTED MATERIALS.
Use of Website. Pacific Scientific Energetic Materials Company (“PacSci EMC”) authorizes you to view and download the materials at this website (“Website”) only for your personal, noncommercial use, provided that you retain on any copies of the materials all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the original materials. The materials at this Website are copyrighted and may also be subject to other legal rights, and unauthorized use of any materials at this Website may violate applicable law. You may not (1) modify the materials at this Website in any way or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose, or (2) make any part of this Website available as part of another website whether by hyperlink or otherwise. For purposes of these Terms, any use of these materials on any other website or networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited.
Links to Other Websites. PacSci EMC does not endorse and makes no representations or warranties whatsoever about any other website which you may choose to access through this Website, or any information, software or other products or materials found there. The links that PacSci EMC provides to such websites are provided solely for your convenience and if you access these links, you will leave this Website and access such links at your own risk. PacSci EMC does not control and is not responsible for any of these websites or their content.
Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability. THE MATERIALS PROVIDED AT THIS WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND INCLUDING WARRANTIES OF QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY. IN NO EVENT WILL PACSCI EMC, IT’S PARENT COMPANY, FORTIVE OR ANY THIRD PARTIES MENTIONED AT THIS WEBSITE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE, INABILITY TO USE, OR THE RESULTS OF USE OF THIS WEBSITE, ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS WEBSITE, OR THE MATERIALS OR INFORMATION CONTAINED AT ANY OR ALL SUCH WEBSITES, WHETHER OR NOT ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES AND/OR THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, SO SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE EXCLUSIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. In addition, PacSci EMC does not warrant (1) that this Website or its server are free from errors or viruses, worms or “Trojan horses,” or (2) the accuracy and completeness of the materials at this Website. The materials at this Website may be out of date, and PacSci EMC makes no commitment to update the materials at this Website. In addition, PacSci EMC may make changes to the materials at this Website at any time without notice.
User Submissions. You are prohibited from transmitting to or from this Website any material that would violate any law. Any information or other communication you transmit to this Website will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary, and PacSci EMC will be free to use such materials for any purpose whatsoever without obligation to you. In particular, PacSci EMC may store your personally identifiable information in hard copy format and electronic media, and in PacSci EMC’s databases that may be located in another country. We will not sell any personal information.
Applicable Laws. PacSci EMC administers this Website from the United States and does not represent or warrant that the materials at this Website are appropriate or available for use outside the United States. Access to this Website and its content from jurisdictions where such content is illegal is prohibited and you may not use, export or re-export the content at this Website or any copy or adaptation in violation of any applicable laws or regulations including without limitation United States export laws and regulations. If you access this Website from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. In addition, information published at this Website may refer to products, programs or services that are not available in your country. These Terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Delaware, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of laws.
General. PacSci EMC may revise these Terms at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page from time to time to review the then-current Terms because they are binding on you. Certain provisions of these Terms may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages at this Website.
Revised December 2018.
Launch me!
SEARCH
Need a quote? We’d love to hear about your project here
Looking for an SDS? Send a request here
Need more information? Let us know how we can help here
Products
Cartridge Actuated Devices
Explosive Bolts | Pyro Fasteners
Frangible Nut – Explosively Separated
Percussion Fired CLCP Initiator
Detonation Booster Assembly (DBA)
Exploding Bridge
Wire – EBW
HNS Initiator – A Percussion Fired Detonator
Fire Extinguisher Squib
Lead Azide Free Detonator – Top Fire Detonator
RF Safe Detonator – GreenDet™ Lead Free
Laser Ordnance Devices
Laser Detonator – Robust and Optimized
Laser Firing Units – Light Weight & Reliable
Laser Initiator – Compact Safety & Reliability
Laser Initiated Ordnance System (LIOS)
Laser Motor Igniter – Rocket Engine Ignition
Networked Electronic Ordnance & Devices
Satellite Deorbit & Precision Re-entry
Satellite Propulsion System – Flight Proven
Satellite Sequencing System – Satellite Dispensing
SEA™ Network Interface – Flexible & Adaptable
Smart Initiator | Digital Intelligent Initiator
Energetics & Chemical Synthesis Solutions
Flexible Confined Detonating Cord
Flexible Detonating Cord (FDC)
Flexible Linear Shaped Charge (FLSC)
High Pressure Shielded Mild Detonating Cord
Inter-Connect Assembly – Emergency Escape
Linear Shaped Charge – Precision Severance
Manifolds & Connectors – EES Sequencing
Mild Detonating Cord (MDC)
Mode Selector | Explosive Sequence Control
Rocket Stage, Payload & Fairing Separation
Rapid Deflagrating Cord (RDC) – Metal Clad Cord
Rapid Deflagrating Cord Transfer Line (RDCTL)
Shielded Mild Detonating Cord – Rigid Det Cord
Propellant Actuated Devices – Compact & Trusted
Hot Gas Initiator – Emergency Escape Systems
Inertia Reel Gas Generator | Aerospace
Pyrotechnic Gas Generator – Compact & Reliable
Start Cartridge – Turbojet Engine Start
Pyrotechnic Igniters – Heat or Pressure Ignition
Hydrogen Burn-Off Igniters for Launch Vehicles
Military Aircraft Emergency Escape & Ejection
What Is A Flight Termination System?
What Is A Typical Emergency Escape System Sequence?
Careers
Products
Cartridge Actuated Devices
Explosive Bolts | Pyro Fasteners
Frangible Nut – Explosively Separated
Hot Bridge Wire | Electro-Explosive Devices
Impulse Cartridge | Precise & Reliable
Pressure Cartridge – Fast, High Rate Pressure
Percussion Fired CLCP Initiator
Detonation Booster Assembly (DBA)
Exploding Bridge
Wire – EBW
HNS Initiator – A Percussion Fired Detonator
Fire Extinguisher Squib
Lead Azide Free Detonator – Top Fire Detonator
RF Safe Detonator – GreenDet™ Lead Free
Laser Ordnance Devices
Laser Detonator – Robust and Optimized
Laser Firing Units – Light Weight & Reliable
Laser Initiator – Compact Safety & Reliability
Laser Initiated Ordnance System (LIOS)
Laser Motor Igniter – Rocket Engine Ignition
Networked Electronic Ordnance & Devices
Satellite Deorbit & Precision Re-entry
Satellite Propulsion System – Flight Proven
Satellite Sequencing System – Satellite Dispensing
SEA™ Network Interface – Flexible & Adaptable
Smart Initiator | Digital Intelligent Initiator
Energetics & Chemical Synthesis Solutions
Flexible Confined Detonating Cord
Flexible Detonating Cord (FDC)
Flexible Linear Shaped Charge (FLSC)
High Pressure Shielded Mild Detonating Cord
Inter-Connect Assembly – Emergency Escape
Linear Shaped Charge – Precision Severance
Manifolds & Connectors – EES Sequencing
Mild Detonating Cord (MDC)
Mode Selector | Explosive Sequence Control
Rocket Stage, Payload & Fairing Separation
Rapid Deflagrating Cord (RDC) – Metal Clad Cord
Rapid Deflagrating Cord Transfer Line (RDCTL)
Shielded Mild Detonating Cord – Rigid Det Cord
Propellant Actuated Devices – Compact & Trusted
Hot Gas Initiator – Emergency Escape Systems
Inertia Reel Gas Generator | Aerospace
Pyrotechnic Gas Generator – Compact & Reliable
Start Cartridge – Turbojet Engine Start
Pyrotechnic Igniters – Heat or Pressure Ignition
Hydrogen Burn-Off Igniters for Launch Vehicles
Military Aircraft Emergency Escape & Ejection
What Is A Flight Termination System?
What Is A Typical Emergency Escape System Sequence?
Careers
Enter your text here
Join PacSci EMC
Sign up
Already have an account? Login
Login to PacSci EMC
Login
Lost Password?
Don't have an account? Sign Up
Reset Password
Enter the username or e-mail you used in your profile. A password reset link will be sent to you by email.
Get new password
Already have an account?								Login
This website uses cookiesWe use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use our our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners
who may combine it with other information that you've provided to them or that they've collected from your use of their services. Use necessary cookies only Allow all Cookies Privacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non Necessary
non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Other
other
Analytics
analytics
Functional
functional
Advertisement
advertisement
